{"data":[{"question":"Your mother was just ______ me that when you came.","a":"telling","b":"saying","c":"say","d":"tell","answer":"1","explain":"- You say something\n\n- You tell someone something\n\n-  Past continuous: be + Verb ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"He didn't ______ us anything.","a":"say","b":"told","c":"said","d":"tell","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Negative in Past continuous tense: Did not + Verb ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What is that man ______?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"telling","d":"saying","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- Past continuous tense: Was\/were + Verb_ing ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"______ me all your problems.","a":"Tell","b":"Say","c":"Told","d":"Said","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What did they ______ about the weather?","a":"tell","b":"say","c":"told","d":"said","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- What\/which + did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you _______.","a":"say","b":"tell","c":"said","d":"told","answer":"1","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- What\/which + did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There were _______ people there!","a":"so much","b":"so many","c":"so","d":"as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"many\" or \"few\" plus a plural noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We've got ______ tea!","a":"so","b":"so much","c":"so many","d":"much","answer":"2","explain":"\n- \"So\" can be combined with \"many\" or \"few\" plus a plural noun to show extremes in amount. This form is often used in exclamations","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you ______ last night?","a":"said","b":"say","c":"tell","d":"told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- You say something \n- You tell someone something \n- What\/which + did + S + V-infinitive + O? ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"This child is ______ big!","a":"so many","b":"so","c":"so much","d":"as","answer":"2","explain":"- So + adjectives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"12","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}